[theme music playing]
[gunshots]
[gun clicks, fires]
[whoosh, slashing sounds]
[machine gun fire]
[machine gun fire continues]
[single gunshot]
[rapid gunfire]
[echoing blast]
[blade whooshing]
[tense music builds]
I shed blood, sweat, and tears
to establish Poblacion Ardiente.
So, blood, sweat, and tears
will spill over
the land they took from me.
[Camia] I do hope this is the end
and not the beginning
of an even bigger battle.
If they come back,
I'll make sure
to take everything they have,
so they can pay for all their crimes.
[Diego] We will wipe away
all the filth left in our town.
Then, we will create a new
Poblacion Ardiente together!
[crowd] Diego! Diego!
-[gunshots]
-[crowd shrieking]
Diego.
[Emilia] Where do we go now, Papa?
Everyone hates us.
We've got nowhere to run.
[Julio] Just drive.
I already know where to go.
Diego! Diego… [sobbing]
He's gone. Diego's gone.
[tense music playing]
[somber music playing]
[exhales]
I'll stay here for a while, Mom.
Are you sure, dear?
[breathes deeply]
All right.
[somber music playing]
[door closes]
[exhales]
[somber music playing]
[sniffles]
[sobbing]
[Diego] Let's enjoy the night.
Because first thing tomorrow,
we'll continue working towards our dream
of having a peaceful and happy town.
We will live in Ardiente.
We'll raise our children here.
We'll start a family here.
Your dream is my dream too.
Remember, Diego.
It's you and me. Till the end.
[somber music playing]
[sobbing]
-[sentimental music playing]
-[sobbing]
[Diego] Even though I've left this world…
I'll always be in your heart.
I'll watch over you…
["Hindi Kita Iiwan" playing]
["Hindi Kita Iiwan" continues playing]
["Hindi Kita Iiwan" instrumental playing]
Diego. [sobbing]
Diego.
["Hindi Kita Iiwan" instrumental playing]
[sobbing]
[tense music playing]
You can stay here while in hiding.
You'll be safe.
Mr. dela Torre will see you
as soon as he gets here.
He's with the Triad leaders in Korea.
Thank you for helping us.
If not for you, we are doomed.
You can thank your father for calling us.
You're the daughter of Red Dragon.
You're one of us.
And the Triad is here to help.
[tense music playing]
[sighs]
[exhales sharply]
[groans]
Papa?
[breathes deeply]
The shocking video
of Lily Cruz's public torture
has finally been released.
[woman] They hid that video for so long.
It wouldn't have been made public
if it weren't for Governor Diego's death.
The Ardientes are cruel to the bone!
We want justice!
We apologize to our viewers.
Here's a portion of the gruesome video.
[clamoring]
We condemn the actions
of Governor Julio Ardiente.
It's sad that these kinds
of actions are still happening.
What they did is cruel. They're monsters.
This is barbaric.
No public official can act
as an executioner.
This should've followed due process.
[Julianna] The Ardientes took
the law into their hands.
This act of cruelty must stop now.
Public officials are obligated
to protect human rights.
Arrest the Ardientes!
They don't deserve their positions!
We will hunt you down.
[tense music playing]
[crowd cheering]
Viva Ardiente!
-Viva Ardiente!
[crowd cheering]
[tense music playing]
Is this it?!
Is this the punishment you're giving me?!
Yes, I killed a lot of people!
I made them all suffer!
But they all deserved to die
because they can be considered
the scums of the earth!
I was just trying to help you
make this godforsaken province
a better place to live in!
[breathes deeply]
I was getting rid
of the worthless bastards
in this world.
And I…
If I have to do it all over again…
-[canes clatter]
-Yes, I would do it!
Because I…
I am Julio Ardiente!
And if anyone goes against me,
I'll send them back to you
with a bullet in their head!
Do you hear me?!
Punish me if you want!
I was just trying
to make this a better place!
Don't you see?!
Those people I killed were worse than me!
They were far worse than me!
[sobbing]
[breathes deeply]
["Walang Hanggang Paalam"
by Joey Ayala playing]
continues playing]
NEW ARDIENTE
["Walang Hanggang Paalam"
continues playing]
[Lily] My journey has led me
into the darkness,
so I could see the light.
The darkness in Diego's death,
and suffering in the hands
of the Ardientes.
[Diego] We'll make our dreams come true.
You and me,
we'll rebuild Poblacion Ardiente.
You are my life, Diego.
You are my governor.
You are the governor of this province.
I love you so much.
I love you so much too, Diego.
[soft guitar music playing]
I am your wife.
But this town is your mother.
I'm not the only one who loves you,
but the people as well.
And I promise to love this town
like how you loved the people of Ardiente.
A love like the one I have for you.
Never-ending.
Eternal.
["Walang Hanggang Paalam"
by Joey Ayala playing]
[dramatic music playing]
Goodbye, Diego.
I love you so much.
[unsettling music playing]
[Julio] Hmm.
[sighs] Papa.
Don't worry about that human rights group.
You know, they just love to bark.
But they can't bite us. So, don't worry.
Because when Stefano comes,
the Triad will help us.
I like your fighting spirit.
Actually, I'm glad
you're finally displaying
the heart of a true Ardiente.
You know, if you remember…
only the weak…
can be conquered by fear.
And we'll never be weak.
[reporter] Hundreds of people
have been continuously coming
to take part in the hero's
burial of the People's Governor
of Poblacion Ardiente, Diego Torillo.
We can clearly see
the unity of the whole town.
Those ingrates!
[Julio scoffs]
Who gave them the right
to have a parade of that…
that bastard's corpse?
Huh?
That animal has no right to be governor!
No right! I'm the only one
who has the right
to be the governor of Poblacion Ardiente!
I'm the only king!
I am the only king!
And no one else can claim my crown.
All of you…
You're just a bunch of good-for-nothings!
-[thuds]
-[glass shattering]
[clapping] Go, Papa!
Show them that you are the one
and only king of Ardiente!
I am!
I am the only king of Ardiente!
No one else!
-Yes.
-Definitely not…
that dead bastard.
[tense music playing]
[somber music playing]
Lily.
I know very well how you're feeling.
I also felt that
when your dad passed away.
[young Lily] Mom, you haven't
gone to work for weeks.
What's going to happen to us now?
[shouts] I don't know!
-[sobbing]
-Please don't cry.
Mom. Please don't cry.
[Camia] But you took care of me…
even when I lost myself.
Lily, remember…
I'll never abandon you.
Don't let the hatred consume your heart.
Don't be like the people who killed Diego.
No matter how grave their crime was…
that doesn't give you the right
to take their lives.
They're the ones who had no right.
They had no right to take
Diego away from me.
None!
They took away my life.
So, not even their deaths
would be punishment enough
for what they did to Diego.
[tense music playing]
[waves crashing]
[camera shutter clicks]
[tense music playing]
-[Emilia] Auntie!
-[gunshot]
[Emilia] No!
[screams] Auntie!
[gunshot]
[suspenseful music playing]
[screaming, wailing]
-[explosion]
-Mama!
[suspenseful music playing]
Be strong, Emilia. Your Papa needs you.
We'll take back everything
that was stolen from us.
[tense music playing]
Papa?
[Julio] Mm?
-[soft thud]
-[clicks tongue]
It's time to celebrate.
Do you know that
I was just talking to Stefano?
-And he's coming.
-Wow.
And he's bringing with him a whole army
that we can use to attack
the people who drove us away.
If I can't have my province back,
I will make sure
that no one else can have it.
The lands of Ardiente
will run red with blood.
Perfect, Papa.
Give them the punishment
that they deserve.
Oh, they will get the punishment
And we will get back
what is rightfully ours.
You and me.
We'll be the ones who'll carry on running
your mother's syndicate.
And the people of Ardiente
won't be the only ones kneeling before us.
Even you.
Because I'm coming for you.
[chuckles]
[tense music playing]
[ominous music playing]
[no audible dialogue]
[tense music playing]
-Emilia.
-Stefano.
-And Governor Ardiente.
-Hey, Stefano.
-[chuckles]
-Welcome, welcome.
Just a little token of appreciation…
for being able to grace
this lovely afternoon
with your presence.
Now this…
[loads rifle]
This is the kind of weapon…
…that will basically turn
any enemy into dust.
[loads rifle]
This is payback for all who
disrespected the administration
that fed them and their families.
I may have fallen,
but like the legendary bird, the phoenix,
I shall once again rise from the ashes.
More beautiful, more powerful than ever.
And everyone who disrespected my name…
will fall on their knees.
Watch out!
I'm coming back, your Señor Julio.
All hail the return of the king.
And of course…
with my queen of Poblacion Ardiente…
-my very own Emilia.
-[Emilia chuckles]
[Stefano] Then…
The alliance between the Triad
and the Ardiente family is now official.
-Mm-hm.
-[Julio] Good.
It has been decided…
that the new leader of this organization
is none other than…
Emilia Ardiente.
I swear I wasn't expecting this, Papa.
[laughs] Thank you.
Mama Red Dragon, I love you.
Thank you for the trust and the chance
that you've given me with this job.
I promise that I'm going
to do good and… thank you.
I love you, Mama. I love you.
-And to you, Papa.
-Yes?
[chuckles softly]
Pa…
I know we talked about
running this syndicate together.
Now that they gave this to me,
I promise to run this
the same way you would have.
I hope you're proud of me, Papa.
[clicks tongue] Of course.
I am very proud of you, Emilia.
Very, very proud.
Thank you, Papa.
[Emilia sighs]
Let's not waste any time!
We will march to Poblacion Ardiente,
and we will take the town
back to Ardiente!
Because Ardiente is for the Ardientes!
-Viva Ardiente!
[Stefano] Don't worry, Governor.
You'll still be protected by the Triad.
-I trust you, Stefano.
-[chuckles]
[suspenseful music]
This is it, Emilia.
You have Papa's trust and love.
Get going, big girl.
Get ready for world domination.
[suspenseful music playing]
I'll be in control of the Triad soon.
I'll finally get you back,
my sweet old town.
Hang tight.
Señor Julio is coming.
We're gonna have a big project tomorrow.
-Excellent.
-Yes, we will.
Okay? So, you better tell
your men and the boys. Be ready.
-We will.
-We will be ready
to take over the town.
-Thank you. [chuckles]
-[man 1] Yeah, no problem.
[man 1] As always.
-[man speaking indistinctly]
-[Emilia chuckles]
Good job.
[tense music playing]
You know, every time
I say that, someone dies.
[chuckles]
[exhales]
No one dared to defy me.
They all loved me.
They even called me their friend.
You know…
I could still be the governor
if Papa didn't tell me to step down.
But you're still here.
Not as a governor…
but one of the leaders
of the most powerful organization in Asia.
[chuckles]
[suspenseful music playing]
[suspenseful music continues]
[Emilia chuckles]
[tense music playing]
[chuckles]
[Stefano] Come in.
I prepared…
something for you.
[tense music playing]
[chuckles] Wait. Wait. Wait.
I'll have to take a shower.
Perfect.
[tense music playing]
I'll be waiting here.
-Okay.
-Make it quick.
[chuckles]
Very quick. [chuckles]
[door closes]
[suspenseful music playing]
Stefano, we need to talk.
Stefano, wait.
[suspenseful music playing]
We have nothing to talk about, Julio.
It has been decided.
How dare you!
You know what I want to talk about.
You know what I want.
[tense music building]
What's happening here?
Indulge me.
What?
You are going to shoot me?
You think you can beat me, huh?
Just because you're supposed
to be a member of the Triad?
No one beats me,
especially an amateur like you.
You know what?
Everyone who goes against me ends up dead.
And I think I will add your head
to the chain of other heads
that I already have.
And I will use you as décor
for my front porch.
[laughs]
You talk too much
for someone so powerless.
[Stefano laughs]
Reality check.
The Triad
is under Emilia now.
And one more thing,
ex-governor.
You're powerless,
and you can't do anything about it.
You are nothing but dirt
under the sole of your own daughter.
[laughs]
[tense music playing]
[chuckles]
[both laugh]
[laughs]
Boys.
[cane clatters]
[tense music playing]
[chuckles]
[suspenseful music playing]
[Julio] What?
Surprise, surprise.
So, you think I am dirt, huh?
Me?! Dirt?!
Emilia is nothing but a stupid weakling.
She actually thinks
that I'm impressed and proud of her.
Well, it's not surprising.
She takes after her mother.
They're no different from each other.
They're both stupid.
Five million each for your allegiance.
[suspenseful music playing]
[sobbing]
Not again, Papa. Not again. [sobbing]
[wailing] I thought you believed
in me this time!
[wailing]
You know…
It was quick thinking on my part
when I put a bomb
in Helena's little ambulance.
[Julio] Bomb.
Boom! [chuckles]
And instantly…
she was dead.
And no one ever knew that I did it.
Now, wasn't that brilliant of me, huh?
Yes!
I am the fire that engulfed…
your precious Red Dragon.
Now…
I want you to listen.
And listen well.
I want this to ring out loud and clear.
It was I.
I killed Red Dragon.
[laughs]
[screams]
Papa, how could you?! You monster!
You bastard!
-[suspenseful music playing]
-[boat engine revving]
[suspenseful music playing]
I murdered Helena.
And if I could do that,
I can kill my own daughter too,
just to get what I want.
Which is…
the Triad's power.
The Triad's money,
the Triad's weapons,
and the Triad's henchmen.
And I am willing to go through anything
to get my kingdom back.
At any cost, Stefano. At any cost.
[suspenseful music playing]
[Arthur] Lily…
Here's what you asked for.
The Triad has decided to work
with the Ardientes.
And from what I heard,
Emilia and Julio
will take over the syndicate.
I know exactly how their minds work.
They will get back at everyone.
And, you're at the top
of their list, Lily.
[suspenseful music playing]
[Jepoy] You can't go in here.
[Natalie] Why the hell not?! Huh?
Let me in!
Hi.
Jepoy.
Hello, Lily Cruz.
Yes, it's me again.
Okay. So, it looks like I barged into
one of the greatest connivances ever.
And I think I'll be joining you, guys.
You found the Ardientes, didn't you?
You found Julio and Emilia.
Stay out of this, Natalie.
You know, I would love
to do that, but I can't.
I have to decide for both of us
and set aside our pride.
We have the same enemies, Lily.
It doesn't make sense for us
to, like, not be in one team, right?
You know what?
It's either that
or I can sabotage your plan.
And we both know that
you wouldn't want that, right?
[squeals]
I guess that's a yes. Silence means yes.
So, yeah. I guess we're teammates now.
Hi, teammate.
Right?
I'll leave you to it.
I don't really have friends, you know?
So, I think we all can be friends now.
[sighs]
You know, I was planning to shoot you.
But
I'll give you your life.
Go back to your bosses in the Triad,
and explain to them
how you lost to a certain Julio Ardiente.
[laughs]
But on second thought…
[gunshots]
[yelps]
[suspenseful music playing]
[breathes deeply]
I think you're better off dead.
[grunts]
[gunshots]
-[Jepoy grunts]
-[woman gasps]
[water splashes]
[gunshot]
[grunts]
[grunts, pants]
-[gunshot]
-[water splashes]
-[gunshots]
[gunshots]
Go! Go! Go!
[Lily] Where do you think
you're going, Julio Ardiente?!
I won't let you ruin any more lives again.
The question is, are you willing to kill?
[screams]
You have an immaculate heart.
You want to be a hero.
That's why you can't push yourself
to soil your hands with blood.
[gunshot]
I am no hero.
That's why I can kill you.
[theme music playing]